PROFILE

I am an accomplished Digital Project Manager with over a decade of experience helping clientele like ESPN, Sykes Enterprises, and Honda grow their business. As a seasoned professional my goals are simple: reduce headaches and create meaningful experiences.

EXPERTISE

- Customer Service Management (SetMore, ZenDesk, Zopim)
- Data Analysis & Collection (Google Forms, Survey Monkey)
- Digital Media Design (Adobe Creative Suite)
- **Ecommerce** (Amazon Seller Central, Stripe)
- Internet Marketing (Campaign Monitor, Hootsuite, Yelp)
- Project Management (Agile, Basecamp, Jira)
- User Experience Design (InVision, Proto.io, UsabilityHub)
- Web Development (CSS, HTML, Javascript, Wordpress)
- Webmaster (FTP, GitHub, Google Analytics)

EXPERIENCE

Hudson's Furniture • Digital Consultant (Contract) • 2015-Present

- Digital Strategist and Social Media Adviser for the executive leadership.
- Developed branded surveys that evaluate customer satisfaction and intelligently displays proper communication channels based upon response sentiment.
- Webmaster and Content Manager for the corporate ecommerce website and all Google My Business and Yelp profiles.

MerchBee · Project Manager (Contract) · 2016

- Directly managed a globally distributed team of 9 members.
- Developed key wireframe sequences and conducted usability testing.
- Webmaster and Content Manager for the corporate website.
- Established customer service and technical support systems.
- Developed branded surveys to collect new feature requests from and evaluate the overall satisfaction of MerchBee's community.

Tupperware • Instructional Designer (Contract) • 2015

• Collaborated with the Group President of Tupperware Americas to create keynote presentations outlining major corporate initiatives for 2016.

Honda • Senior User Experience Designer (Contract) • 2015

 Designed complete wireframe sequences and conducted usability testing within simulated roadside assistance situations.

Sykes Enterprises • User Experience Designer (Contract) • 2015

- Oversaw 3 enterprise-scale projects as Project Manager and directly managed multifaceted teams exceeding 15 members.
- Collaborated with executive leadership to translate business strategies into

- applications that support over 40,000 active employees.
- Developed key wireframe sequences and interactive prototypes then conducted on-site usability tests with groups exceeding 100 users.

Telespeak • Director of Marketing • 2014-2015

- Rebranded entire company including all products and services.
- Designed, developed, and deployed the fully responsive company website (inactive).
- Developed and deployed weekly email campaigns to over 33,000 subscribers.
- Created print ads and authored articles for ChannelVision Magazine.
- Designed company trade show booth and attendee experience.

Full Sail University • Lab Specialist • 2011-2014

- Facilitated learning and enhanced curriculum across 13 courses including Web
 Interface & Usability, Designing for Web Standards, and Rich Media Optimization.
- Updated curriculum to reflect best practices and address feedback.
- Led monthly extracurricular lectures on branding, color theory, and user experience.
- Marketed and formed partnerships with industry leaders including Designzillas, Push, and Rackspace to provide graduates with quality career opportunities.

ESPN • Producer (Contract) • 2011-2012

- Directed event coverage, managed diverse production staff, and led star athlete interviews for Twirl Mania 2011, the largest baton twirling competition in the US.
- Produced the ESPN3 broadcasted 2011 Diamond Citrus Classic promos.
- Motionographer that handled animations and bumpers for the ESPN Rise Games.
- Produced highlights for the 2011 Contest of Champions Nationals that collectively received over 250,000 views in 30 days on YouTube.

RECOGNITION

Throughout my career I have received over 20 awards, including numerous Site of the Day awards from organizations like CSS Gallery and Design Shack. I have also been recognized in industry publications including InstantShift and Top Design Mag.

EDUCATION

Full Sail University • Entertainment Business Master's • 2010-2011

 Received the Course Director Award for Brand & Storytelling Development from Ken DeGilio who said "You truly understand how to build complete brand experiences."

Full Sail University • Digital Arts & Design Bachelor's • 2006-2008

• Featured Artist in Full Sail University's 2007 Art Gala.